http://www.suntekstore.com/article-28-privacy_policy.html

|Order Tracking
Hot Searches: iPhone 5 Sunglasses Microphone Car Lights HDMI iPhone 4S
All categories
ElectronicsClothing & AccessoriesComputer HardwaresJewelries & WatchesCell Phone & AccessoriesHome, Garden & OfficeToys & GamesSurveillance & SecurityCameras & CamcordersCar AccessoriesOutdoors & SportsApple AccessoriesHealth & BeautyNoveltiesVideo Games AccessoriesSolar ProductsChristmas Sale
All Categories
Electronics
close
Electronics
Musical Instruments
Guitar
Bass Guitar
Violin
My Cart
Your shopping cart is empty.
Home > Customer Service > Privacy Policy
Help Center
Customer Service
Contact Us
Return Policy
FAQ
Privacy Policy
Payment & Shipping
Privacy Policy
We appreciate the trust from customers in releasing information. Customer privacy is our first priority. We strongly believe that customers have the right to know how we use their information. The following privacy statement will help you to learn more about how we use, where we use and who manages your information.
All customer information collected via the site is for any business or operational practices within our company only. Customer information will not be revealed or resold to other firms. Our employees agree only to use information in order to provide superior customer service.
Customers have the right to refuse disclosing privacy information. However, customers must understand that some information is required to become a registered site visitor, and for order processing purposes.
Customer Service
>>Contact Us
>>Return Policy
>>FAQ
>>Privacy Policy
Payment & Shipping
>>Payment Methods
>>Shipping & Delivery
